<modDesc descVersion="94">
    <author>Beeves</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Dynamic Economy</en>
        <de>Dynamische Wirtschaft</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[
Dynamic Economy will adjust the market prices for each product, crop, or animal type based on a supply-and-demand system.

The market demands an annual supply of each product type. Roughly €75,000 worth on hard. €135,000 on medium, and €225,000 on easy. Doubled if seasonal growth is disabled.

Selling more than the demanded amount will decrease the prices of a product due to the overabundance. Selling less will increase the prices due to the scarcity.

The prices can range between 40% and 120% of normal values.

A minimum 4-hour grace period allows for selling without immediate negative impacts to prices.

When an operation becomes large enough to produce the amount of product demanded by the market, it is no longer as profitable to expand that operation any further. The goal is to encourage you to branch out into new types of jobs as your farm grows and create a unique competitive element in multiplayer games.
        ]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[
Dynamische Wirtschaft passt die Marktpreise für jedes Produkt, jede Kulturpflanze oder jeden Tiertyp basierend auf einem Angebot-und-Nachfrage-System an.

Der Markt verlangt eine jährliche Versorgung für jeden Produkttyp: etwa 75.000 € auf Schwierigkeitsgrad "Schwer", 135.000 € auf "Mittel" und 225.000 € auf "Leicht". Die Nachfrage verdoppelt sich, wenn das saisonale Wachstum deaktiviert ist.

Wenn Sie mehr als die geforderte Menge verkaufen, sinken die Preise eines Produkts aufgrund eines Überangebots. Weniger zu verkaufen führt aufgrund von Knappheit zu höheren Preisen.

Die Preise können zwischen 40 % und 120 % des Normalwerts schwanken.

Eine Mindestnachfrist von 4 Stunden ermöglicht den Verkauf ohne unmittelbare negative Auswirkungen auf die Preise.

Wenn ein Betrieb groß genug wird, um die vom Markt geforderte Menge zu produzieren, wird es weniger profitabel, denselben Betrieb weiter auszubauen. Das Ziel besteht darin, Sie zu ermutigen, mit dem Wachstum Ihres Hofs neue Berufsfelder zu erschließen und ein einzigartiges Wettbewerbselement in Multiplayer-Spielen hinzuzufügen.
        ]]></de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_dynamicEconomy.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="script.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>
