<modDesc descVersion="94">
    <author>Beeves</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Supply and Demand</en>
        <de>Angebot und Nachfrage</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[
Adjusts the market prices for each product, crop, or animal type based on a supply-and-demand system.

The market demands an annual supply of each product type. Roughly €75,000 worth on hard. €135,000 on medium, and €225,000 on easy. Doubled if seasonal growth is disabled.

Selling more than the demanded amount will decrease the prices of a product due to the overabundance. Selling less will increase the prices due to the scarcity.

The prices can range between 40% and 120% of normal values.

A minimum 4-hour grace period allows for selling without immediate negative impacts to prices.

When an operation becomes large enough to produce the amount of product demanded by the market, it is no longer as profitable to expand that operation any further. The goal is to encourage you to branch out into new types of jobs as your farm grows and create a unique competitive element in multiplayer games.
        ]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[
Passt die Marktpreise für jedes Produkt, jede Kultur oder jeden Tiertyp auf der Grundlage eines Angebots- und Nachfragesystems an.

Der Markt verlangt von jedem Produkttyp eine jährliche Versorgung. Etwa 75.000 € wert auf hart. 135.000 € für die mittlere Variante und 225.000 € für die leichte Variante. Wird verdoppelt, wenn das saisonale Wachstum deaktiviert ist.

Wenn Sie mehr als die geforderte Menge verkaufen, sinken die Preise eines Produkts aufgrund des Überangebots. Weniger zu verkaufen führt aufgrund der Knappheit zu höheren Preisen.

Die Preise können zwischen 40 % und 120 % des Normalwertes liegen.

Eine Nachfrist von mindestens 4 Stunden ermöglicht den Verkauf ohne unmittelbare negative Auswirkungen auf die Preise.

Wenn ein Betrieb groß genug wird, um die vom Markt geforderte Produktmenge zu produzieren, ist es nicht mehr so ​​profitabel, diesen Betrieb weiter auszubauen. Das Ziel besteht darin, Sie zu ermutigen, mit dem Wachstum Ihrer Farm neue Berufsfelder zu erschließen und ein einzigartiges Wettbewerbselement in Multiplayer-Spielen zu schaffen.
        ]]></de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_supplyAndDemand.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="supplyAndDemand.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>
